let questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of music notation?",
    options: [
      " Standard notation",
      " Tab notation",
      "  Morse code notation",
      "Graphics notation",
    ],
    answer: "C.Morse code notation",
    category: "music",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "What is the most common time signature in classical music?",
    options: ["A.3/4", "B.4/4", "C.5/4", "D.6/8"],
    answer: "B.4/4",
    category: "music",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "Which of the following is not a type of instrument in a symphony orchestra?",
    options: ["Violin", "Piano", "Harp", "Theremin"],
    answer: "Theremin",
    category: "music",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What is the most common key in pop music?",
    options: ["C Major", "G Major", "D Major", "A Major"],
    answer: "C Major",
    category: "music",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of chord?",
    options: ["Major", "Minor", "Diminished", "Flat"],
    answer: "Flat",
    category: "music",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of music genre?",
    options: ["Jazz", "Blues", "Rock", "Applesauce"],
    answer: "Applesauce",
    category: "music",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of music theory?",
    options: ["Harmony", "Counterpoint", "Form", "Cooking"],
    answer: "Cooking",
    category: "music",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is the most common tempo marking in classical music?",
    options: ["Allegro", "Andante", "Adagio", "Moderato"],
    answer: "Allegro",
    category: "music",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of musical form?",
    options: ["Sonata", "Symphony", "Concerto", "Spaghetti"],
    answer: "Spaghetti",
    category: "music",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "Which of the following is not a type of music notation software?",
    options: ["Sibelius", "Finale", "MuseScore", "Microsoft Word"],
    answer: "Microsoft Word",
    category: "music",
  },
];
